{
  "applicant": "369d4cce-70a7-4bc4-8f2c-06847d364d96",
  "answers": [
    {
      "question": "mothersMaidenName",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "fra"
    },
    {
      "question": "registrationEmailAddress",
      "answerType": "emailSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "type": "Home",
          "address": "access1@Test.com",
          "order": 0,
          "rhtyh": {
            "type": "Work",
            "address": "work1@Test.com",
            "order": 2
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "Work",
          "address": "work1@Test.com",
          "order": 2,
          "rhtyh": {
            "type": "Work",
            "address": "work1@Test.com",
            "order": 2
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "humanReadableId",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "IBB369d4cc"
    },
    {
      "question": "crossBorderCriteriaId",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "a7c4193e-3d4e-4499-8599-3c3866e11718"
    },
    {
      "question": "emailAddresses",
      "answerType": "emailSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "type": "Home",
          "address": "access1@Test.com",
          "order": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "jointAccountQuestion",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Sole account"
    },
    {
      "question": "areYouMovingInTheNextTwoMonths",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "currentlyApplyingForABarclaysMortgage",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "applicationId",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "369d4cce-70a7-4bc4-8f2c-06847d364d96"
    },
    {
      "question": "sourceOfFundsNotesAndCoins",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "dateOfBirth",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "1996-10-07"
    },
    {
      "question": "areYouAUSCitizen",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "websiteForFasterProcessing",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "sourceOfFundsInitialDeposit",
      "answerType": "money",
      "answer": {
        "currency": "GBP",
        "amount": "56757"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "accountSelector",
      "answerType": "accountSelectorSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "accountHolderId": "369d4cce-70a7-4bc4-8f2c-06847d364d96",
          "chequeNo": "0",
          "location": "Isle of Man",
          "capitalProductsType": [],
          "cardHolder": "",
          "productType": "InternationalBankAcc",
          "chequeName": "",
          "currency": "EUR",
          "productId": "11c3c001-0932-4bf2-a485-093ed5c0a1c4",
          "cardName": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "methodsOfContactForMarketingPreferences",
      "answerType": "stringSet",
      "answer": []
    },
    {
      "question": "countryOfBirth",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "France"
    },
    {
      "question": "haveYouHadAnyOtherNamesInThePast",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "salesforceRequestStatus",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "registrationStepDone"
    },
    {
      "question": "lastName",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "fra"
    },
    {
      "question": "firstName",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "shivamprop"
    },
    {
      "question": "primaryAccount",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "relationshipStatus",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Single"
    },
    {
      "question": "userAgents",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; WOW64) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/85.0.4183.83 Safari/537.36"
    },
    {
      "question": "securityQuestion",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "france"
    },
    {
      "question": "sourceOfWealthOtherInfo",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "wantToUploadDocuments",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Post Documents"
    },
    {
      "question": "workflowState",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "In Progress"
    },
    {
      "question": "accountLocationBI",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Isle of Man"
    },
    {
      "question": "grossAnnualIncome",
      "answerType": "money",
      "answer": {
        "currency": "GBP",
        "amount": "0"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "jumioCounter",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "primaryAddress",
      "answerType": "address",
      "answer": {
        "postCode": "ghfhj",
        "country": "France",
        "line1": "mr",
        "townOrCity": "dfsgsdfg",
        "order": 0,
        "from": "2010-10-07",
        "line2": ""
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "nationality",
      "answerType": "orderedStringSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "value": "France",
          "order": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "doYouAlreadyHoldBarclaysAccountInUK",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "creationDate",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "2020-09-02"
    },
    {
      "question": "occupationStatus",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Not working"
    },
    {
      "question": "sourceOfFundsExpectedAssetsOverTwelveMonths",
      "answerType": "money",
      "answer": {
        "currency": "GBP",
        "amount": "65"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "funds",
      "answerType": "sourceOfFundsDetailSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "source": "Other",
          "description": "jgjk",
          "institution": "",
          "countries": [
            "France"
          ],
          "order": 0,
          "additionalFundDetail": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "middleNames",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "registrationQueryParameters",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "title",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Mr"
    },
    {
      "question": "registrationPasswordJson",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "{\"hash\":\"�0��RV�m���I��Xu\",\"salt\":\"54b45f51-ec46-4c2b-9b2d-c90484ed7647\"}"
    },
    {
      "question": "riskEvaluation",
      "answerType": "riskEvaluation",
      "answer": {
        "type": "IncompleteRiskEvaluation",
        "value": {
          "incompleteRiskAnswers": [
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "sourceOfPersonalWealth",
                "sourceSystem"
              ]
            }
          ],
          "completeRiskAnswers": [
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "otherTelephoneNumbers"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "sourceOfFundsInitialDeposit",
                "sourceOfPersonalWealth"
              ],
              "risk": "NonStandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "optionalMobileNumber"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "primaryAddress"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "occupationStatus",
                "grossAnnualIncome"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "countryTaxDetails"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "sourceOfFundsNotesAndCoins"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "funds"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "sourceOfWealthOtherInfo"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "countryTaxDetails",
                "primaryAddress"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "sourceOfFundsExpectedAssetsOverTwelveMonths"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "countryOfBirth"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "sourceOfPersonalWealth"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "title"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "grossAnnualIncome"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "sourceOfFundsInitialDeposit"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "nationality"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            },
            {
              "questionKey": [
                "nationality",
                "primaryAddress"
              ],
              "risk": "StandardRisk"
            }
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "isThisTheMailingAddress",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "sourceOfPersonalWealth",
      "answerType": "wealthDetailSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "country": [
            "France"
          ],
          "amount": "0",
          "activityType": "Other",
          "order": 0,
          "additionalWealthDetail": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "placeOfBirth",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "france"
    },
    {
      "question": "securityAnswer",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "france"
    },
    {
      "question": "optionalMobileNumber",
      "answerType": "phoneNumberSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "type": "Mobile",
          "countryCode": "33",
          "localNumber": "5346",
          "order": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "sourceSystem",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "IBSS"
    },
    {
      "question": "postalRadioCheckBox",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "gender",
      "answerType": "string",
      "answer": "Male"
    },
    {
      "question": "countryTaxDetails",
      "answerType": "countryTaxDetailsSet",
      "answer": [
        {
          "countryName": "France",
          "tin": "7658698",
          "order": 0
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
